liveistream.tv 2015-02-15

# LiveiStream

## Privacy Policy

LiveiStream and WhiteSmoke highly value your privacy and take all the possible measures to protect your information. Please read the following to learn more about LiveiStream's Privacy Policy ("Policy"). This Policy details how LiveiStream receives, collects and uses information in connection with our website and software provided on the LiveiStream.tv website (the website and software collectively referred to herein as "Site").

**1\. Collection and Use of Information**

1.1. LiveiStream does not automatically collect any personally identifiable information, such as names, e-mail, age, gender, address, telephone numbers, login names and passwords or other self-identifying information ("Personal Information").

1.2. LiveiStream may use cookies on the Site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier and faster by saving preferences and browsing patterns while you are on LiveiStream's Site. Cookies may be used to analyze Site usage, improve content, customize the Site's content and layout and for other customer service purposes. LiveiStream's use of cookies is in no way linked to any Personal Information.

1.3. LiveiStream may automatically receive and record certain non-personally identifiable information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), cookie information, and the webpage that a user visits. LiveiStream collects non-personally identifiable information for general purposes, including but not limited to analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking user movements, conducting research, and providing anonymous reporting to internal and external clients. LiveiStream will not link any Personal Information, including e-mail addresses, with aggregate data of its users.

**2\. Sharing and Disclosure of Information**

LiveiStream does not rent, sell, or share any information about the user with any third-parties. LiveiStream may disclose your Personal Information if LiveiStream believes such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on LiveiStream (b) protect and defend the rights or property of LiveiStream (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of LiveiStream services or members of the public.

**3\. Explicit Content**

You understand that by using the Service, you may encounter content that may be deemed offensive, indecent, or objectionable, which content may or may not be identified as having explicit language. Nevertheless, you agree to use the Site at your sole risk and that LiveiStream shall have no liability to you for content that may be found to be offensive, indecent, or objectionable. LiveiStream shall have no liability or responsibility to you for any content or materials that may be available in connection with the Site that you might find objectionable.

LiveiStream is the sole operator of the LiveiStream.tv Website. However, our website contains links to other sites. LiveiStream assumes no responsibility for the content or the privacy policies and practices of such websites. LiveiStream encourages you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites since their privacy practices may differ from ours. 

**4\. Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of children is especially important. We operate our website in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We never knowingly collect or maintain information at or on our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is directed at or structured to attract anyone under 13. Visitors younger than 13 years of age may NOT use the LiveiStream website and software and must LEAVE immediately.

**5\. Policy Changes**

From time to time, LiveiStream may revise this Policy. LiveiStream will post the revised Policy on the Site, so that users can always be aware of what information LiveiStream collects, how the information is used and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed. 

**6\. Contact Information**

Please direct all questions in connection with this Policy via e-mail to [support@LiveiStream.tv](mailto:support@LiveiStream.tv). You can also write to LiveiStream/WhiteSmoke, Attention: LiveiStream Support, 501 Silverside Rd, Suite 105, Wilmington, DE 19809, USA.
